Rockwell Kent
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Alphabetical Files, circa 1900-1971, undated, Series 1:; (Reels 5153-5249, 5256, 5740-5741)
  - Robert C. Vose Paintings, 1927 (Reel 5244, Frame 1336-1346)
  - Voyaging, 1969 (Reel 5244, Frame 1347-1352)
  - Voznich, Mrs. Wilfred, 1927 (Reel 5244, Frame 1353-1357)
  - V, Illegible (Reel 5244, Frame 1358-1361)
    (Frances Hill Von [N?], 1936)
  - Wagner, Dorothy, 1941 (Reel 5244, Frame 1362-1365)
  - Wagner, T. B., 1919 (Reel 5244, Frame 1366-1371)
  - Wake Up!, 1947-1948 (Reel 5244, Frame 1372-1399)
    (thank-you letters from friends for Christmas gift of lithograph)
  - Walker, Alfred, undated (Reel 5244, Frame 1400-1412)
  - Walker's, 1942 (Reel 5244, Frame 1413-1417)
  - Wallace, Edward J., 1944 (Reel 5244, Frame 1418-1420)
  - Wallace for President Committee, 1948 (Reel 5244, Frame 1421-1423)
  - Wallace, Henry, 1949 (Reel 5244, Frame 1424-1427)
  - Wallace, Lois, 1965 (Reel 5244, Frame 1428-1431)
  - Walsh, Chad, 1939 (Reel 5244, Frame 1432-1438)
  - Walter, Dick H., 1941 (Reel 5244, Frame 1439-1441)
  - Walters, R. Randolph, 1941-1942 (Reel 5244, Frame 1442-1456)
  - Walters, Thorstina, [circa 1935], 1941, 1954 (Reel 5244, Frame 1457-1468)
  - Wandell, Jack, 1951 (Reel 5244, Frame 1469-1473)
  - War Department, 1941, 1943-1944 (Reel 5244, Frame 1474-1506)
    (correspondence with George Biddle, chairman of War Department Art Advisory Committee, mainly about reorganization of postwar Federal Arts Project; see also: Federal Arts Project; WPA Miscellaneous)
  - War Price and Ration Board, 1943 (Reel 5244, Frame 1507-1510)
  - War Shipping Administration, 1944 (Reel 5244, Frame 1511-1513)
  - War Stamp Chain Letter, 1943 (Reel 5244, Frame 1514-1555)
  - Ward, Harry F., 1941 (Reel 5244, Frame 1556-1559)
  - Ward Lumber Company, 1947 (Reel 5244, Frame 1560-1562)
  - Ward, Lynd, and May McNeer, undated, 1941, 1944-1962, 1966-1970 (Reel 5245, Frame 3-28)
  - Ward, Mary F., 1946, 1950 (Reel 5245, Frame 29-32)
  - Ward, Rose and Dan, undated, 1931, 1950-1951 (Reel 5245, Frame 33-46)
  - Ward, Sydney, 1944 (Reel 5245, Frame 47-49)
  - Waring, Fred, 1947 (Reel 5245, Frame 50-55)
  - The Warner Brothers Company Incorporated, Manufacturers, 1927 (Reel 5245, Frame 56-58)
  - Warren, Frances H., 1946 (Reel 5245, Frame 59-61)
  - Washington Committee for Democratic Action, 1941 (Reel 5245, Frame 62-64)
  - Washington Youth Council, 1941 (Reel 5245, Frame 65-68)
  - Watson, Mrs. David, 1948 (Reel 5245, Frame 69-73)
  - Watson, Morris, undated, 1946, 1948-1949, 1955-1961 (Reel 5245, Frame 74-111)
  - Waverly House Publishers, 1941 (Reel 5245, Frame 113-117)
    (target filmed last)
  - Way, Walther Denslow, 1941 (Reel 5245, Frame 118-119)
  - "We Hold These Truths," undated (Reel 5245, Frame 120-141)
    (manuscripts of brief articles for Fraternal Outlook column)
  - WEAF, 1946 (Reel 5245, Frame 142-144)
  - Weatherby, Allen, 1936 (Reel 5245, Frame 145-177)
    (correspondence with family of psychiatric patient cared for by the Kents)
  - Weatherby, Frederick S., 1936, 1942, undated (Reel 5245, Frame 178-186)
  - Weaver, Edith and George Ahqupuk, 1935-1938 (Reel 5245, Frame 187-250)
    (correspondence with and about Ahgupuk, a young Eskimo artist whom Kent represented and promoted)
  - Weaver, John V. A., 1921 (Reel 5245, Frame 251-257)
  - Webb Book Publishing Co., 1942-1943 (Reel 5245, Frame 258-304)
    (correspondence regarding illustrations for various books)
  - Webber, Melvin M., 1939 (Reel 5245, Frame 305-307)
  - Weber, Jim, 1938 (Reel 5245, Frame 308-310)
  - Weber, Max, 1956 (Reel 5245, Frame 311-313)
  - Weber, Palmer, undated, 1957-1960 (Reel 5245, Frame 314-337)
  - Webster, Dr. Daniel, 1955 (Reel 5245, Frame 338-340)
  - Webster, T. Preston, Jr., 1946 (Reel 5245, Frame 341-345)
  - Wedell, Carolyn (see also: Fan Mail), undated (Reel 5245, Frame 346-348)
  - Weeks, Rufus W., 1913-1916 (Reel 5245, Frame 349-378)
  - Wegener, Ernest A., 1944 (Reel 5245, Frame 379-383)
  - Wegmann, Elizabeth, 1950 (Reel 5245, Frame 384-387)
  - Wehs, Mr. and Mrs., 1958 (Reel 5245, Frame 388-392)
  - William Weiner Defense Committee, 1940 (Reel 5245, Frame 488-544)
    (form letters, news releases, and financial statements)
  - Weinstock, Louis, 1958-1961 (Reel 5245, Frame 545-556)
  - Weir, John and Edya, 1963-1970, undated (Reel 5245, Frame 393-482)
  - Weiss, Sid Cohen, undated, 1953-1965 (Reel 5245, Frame 557-614)
  - Weizmann, Dr. Chaim, 1952 (Reel 5245, Frame 615-618)
  - Wellscroft Club, 1947 (Reel 5245, Frame 619-623)
  - Welsh, Margaret A.C., 1941 (Reel 5245, Frame 483-487)
  - Weng, Siegfried and Jerry, 1959, 1962, [1969] (Reel 5245, Frame 624-630)
  - Wernery, Mrs. L. A., 1949 (Reel 5245, Frame 631-634)
  - Wesley, David, 1951-1970 (Reel 5245, Frame 635-1571)
    (correspondence about American press, Wesley's column and editorials in York [Pa.] Gazette; news of mutual friends, and exhibitions; clippings)
  - Wesley, David, cont. (Reel 5246, Frame 2-104)
  - Wesselow, Eric, 1967-1968 (Reel 5246, Frame 105-130)
  - Westchester County and Its People, 1941 (Reel 5246, Frame 131-139)
  - Western Association of Art Museum Directors, 1925 (Reel 5246, Frame 140-142)
  - Western Union Telegraph Company, 1946 (Reel 5246, Frame 143-147)
  - Westport Coal & Supply Company, 1936 (Reel 5246, Frame 148-150)
  - Westport Yacht Club, 1941 (Reel 5246, Frame 151-154)
  - Weygand, James Lamar, 1964-1965 (Reel 5246, Frame 155-159)
  - E. Weyhe, 1903-1953, undated (Reel 5246, Frame 160-730)
    (correspondence with Carl Zigrosser about: family news, prints on consignment, exhibitions, reproduction permissions, and bookplate commissions; contract for exclusive rights; sales reports; lists of works exhibited and consigned, locations of destroyed woodblocks; see also: Zigrosser, Carl)
  - WGA War Broadcasts, 1941 (Reel 5246, Frame 731-733)
  - "What Is an American?", undated (Reel 5246, Frame 734-748)
    (draft and final manuscript of an article by Kent)
  - Wheeler, Steve, 1947 (Reel 5246, Frame 749-752)
  - Whibley, Jenny, 1919, 1963 (Reel 5246, Frame 1023-1028)
  - Whibley vs. Cobb and Kent, 1915 (Reel 5246, Frame 753-1022)
    (legal briefs and transcripts of testimony in a lawsuit over returning remainder of trust fund following death of illegitimate son)
  - Whipple, C., 1944 (Reel 5246, Frame 1029-1031)
  - White Collar Workers Investigation, 1944 (Reel 5246, Frame 1032-1053)
    (correspondence about Senate investigation of living conditions and wages of white collar workers, including artists)
  - White, Rev. Eliot, undated, 1945-1967 (Reel 5246, Frame 1054-1084)
  - White, Henry C., 1941 (Reel 5246, Frame 1085-1088)
  - White, John, undated (Reel 5246, Frame 1089-1092)
  - White, Nelson C., undated, 1941, 1951-1952 (Reel 5246, Frame 1093-1112)
  - Whiteface, 1934, 1941-1942 (Reel 5246, Frame 1113-1235)
    (letters to elected officials and editors protesting plan to construct highway on Whiteface mountain and subsequent plan for ski trails; letters praising Kent's position on the issues; clippings)
  - Whiteface Grange No. 1045, 1944, 1947 (Reel 5246, Frame 1236-1239)
  - Whiteface Inn, undated (Reel 5246, Frame 1240-1242)
  - Whiteface Ski Trail Amendment, 1941-1942 (Reel 5246, Frame 1243-1368)
  - Whiting, Elizabeth [sister of Kathleen Kent], undated, 1941, 1943, 1949-1950 (Reel 5246, Frame 1369-1402)
  - Whitman, Georgia [Lightbody] (see also: Lightbody, Charles and Georgia), 1968, 1970 (Reel 5246, Frame 1403-1410)
  - Walt Whitman Society of America, 1943 (Reel 5246, Frame 1411-1413)
  - Whitney Museum of American Art, 1941-1948, 1961, 1966 (Reel 5246, Frame 1414-1426)
  - Whitney, Dr. Norman J., 1959 (Reel 5246, Frame 1427-1432)
  - Whittaker, Albert R., undated (Reel 5246, Frame 1433-1436)
  - Whitty, Flora, 1943, 1968-1970 (Reel 5246, Frame 1437-1458)
  - Who's Who in Graphic Art, 1959 (Reel 5246, Frame 1465-1474)
  - Who's Who in the East, 1941 (Reel 5246, Frame 1459-1464)
  - Wicher, Maria and Enos, undated, 1945 (Reel 5246, Frame 1475-1482)
  - Wickey, Harry, 1947 (Reel 5246, Frame 1483-1491)
  - Wildenstein & Co., Inc., 1927-1947 (Reel 5246, Frame 1492-1532)
    (correspondence concerning sales and insurance; checklist and announcement for 1927 solo exhibition)
  - Wilder, Elizabeth Forbes, [1962]-1964, 1969 (Reel 5246, Frame 1533-1547)
  - Wilder, Ernestine, 1951 (Reel 5246, Frame 1548-1550)
  - Wilderness, 1911-1932, 1966-1971, undated (Reel 5246, Frame 1551-1600)
    (letters, telegrams and notes regarding trips to Newfoundland and South America; correspondence with agents and publishers regarding reissuing of book)
  - Wilderness, cont. (Reel 5247, Frame 3-489)
  - The Wilderness Society, 1941-1942 (Reel 5247, Frame 490-495)
  - Willard, Howard and Charlotte, 1938-1943, 1950 (Reel 5247, Frame 500-554)
    (correspondence regarding speaking engagements, anti-Coughlin activities)
  - Williams, Mrs. Albert Rhys, 1958 (Reel 5247, Frame 556-558)
  - Williams, Claude, 1944, 1947 (Reel 5247, Frame 559-565)
  - Williams, Gil, 1964-1971, undated (Reel 5247, Frame 566-613)
  - Williams, Margaret, [1943] (Reel 5247, Frame 614-616)
  - Williams, Marian, 1939 (Reel 5247, Frame 617-620)
  - Williams, Roy, 1969 (Reel 5247, Frame 621-625)
  - Williams, Mr. and Mrs. Stanley, 1969 (Reel 5247, Frame 626-629)
  - Williams, Warner, 1941 (Reel 5247, Frame 630-632)
  - Willkie, Wendell L., 1942 (Reel 5247, Frame 496-499)
  - Willoughby Camera Stores, Inc., 1945 (Reel 5247, Frame 633-635)
  - Willoughby, Florance, [1922] (Reel 5247, Frame 636-639)
  - Willy, W., 1941 (Reel 5247, Frame 640-642)
  - Wilson, Cora McDevitt, 1947 (Reel 5247, Frame 643-647)
  - Wilson, Gilbert, 1941, 1943-1944, undated (Reel 5247, Frame 648-707)
    (correspondence about Guggenheim Fellowship application, Art Young, and proposal for mural decoration of chapel)
  - The H. W. Wilson Company (see also: Contemporary American Artists), 1941 (Reel 5247, Frame 708-717)
  - Wilson, Jane, undated, 1947-1957 (Reel 5247, Frame 718-724)
  - Wilson Mechanical Instrument Co., Inc., 1941 (Reel 5247, Frame 725-728)
  - Wilson, Robert A., 1939 (Reel 5247, Frame 729-731)
  - Wilson, Ruth, 1950 (Reel 5247, Frame 732-735)
  - Wilson, Watty, 1949 (Reel 5247, Frame unfilmed)
    (concerning unpaid bills of former employee)
  - Winchester Art Association, 1941 (Reel 5247, Frame 736-739)
  - Windward Islands, 1949 (Reel 5247, Frame 740-791)
  - Wingate, Andrew, 1952 (Reel 5247, Frame 792-794)
  - Winn, Jean, 1939 (Reel 5247, Frame 795-797)
  - Winona Public Library, 1956 (Reel 5247, Frame 798-801)
  - Winslow, Leon L., 1941 (Reel 5247, Frame 802-808)
  - Winter Soldiers, 1941 (Reel 5247, Frame 809-813)
  - WIRY, 1954, 1958 (Reel 5247, Frame 814-817)
  - Wisdom Encyclopedia, 1966 (Reel 5247, Frame 818-826)
  - William H. Wise & Co., 1939-1943 (Reel 5247, Frame 827-923)
    (correspondence and contract concerning work on 100 World Famous Paintings)
  - Wishes, Sylvia, [1943] (Reel 5247, Frame 924-926)
  - Witherell, Jane, undated (Reel 5247, Frame 927-930)
  - Woholtjen, Henry, 1918-1919; 1941-1943 (Reel 5247, Frame 931-968)
  - Wolff, Ernst Victor and Thea, 1941-1947 (Reel 5247, Frame 969-1003)
  - Wolk, Mr., 1955 (Reel 5247, Frame 1004-1006)
  - Woman's National Institute, 1942 (Reel 5247, Frame 1007-1011)
  - Woman's National Republican Club, Inc., 1941 (Reel 5247, Frame 1012-1015)
  - Woman's Press Club of New York City, 1942 (Reel 5247, Frame 1016-1020)
  - Womrath Bookshops and Libraries, Inc., 1946, 1954 (Reel 5247, Frame 1021-1025)
  - Wood, Barbara (Mrs. Benjamin Wood), 1943 (Reel 5247, Frame 1026-1032)
  - Wood, Everett W., 1946 (Reel 5247, Frame 1033-1035)
  - Wood, Mrs. George B., 1948 (Reel 5247, Frame 1036-1039)
  - Woodruff, Chamberlain Hoyt, 1967, 1969 (Reel 5247, Frame 1040-1044)
  - Woodward, Robert Strong, 1947 (Reel 5247, Frame 1045-1047)
  - Woodward Memorial Library (see: Demarais, Dorothy B.) (Reel 5247)
  - The Worker, 1958 (Reel 5247, Frame 1048-1050)
  - Workers Bookshop, 1941, 1943, 1949 (Reel 5247, Frame 1051-1056)
  - Workers Defense League, 1942 (Reel 5247, Frame 1057-1059)
  - Workers Library Publishers, 1943 (Reel 5247, Frame 1060-1062)
  - The World, 1917 (Reel 5247, Frame 1063-1069)
  - World Congress for Peace, 1949-1950 (Reel 5247, Frame 1071-1420)
    (form letters, miscellaneous printed matter, and correspondence about disarmament campaign, demonstrations, and Kent's participation in the group's activities)
  - World Council of Peace, 1952, 1955-1960 (Reel 5247, Frame 1421-1540)
    (correspondence and printed matter [apparently very closely related to World Congress for Peace, possibly a successor organization])
  - World Council of Peace, cont. (Reel 5248, Frame 3-144)
  - World Famous Paintings (see also: Nuts; Welsh, Margaret A. C.), undated (Reel 5248, Frame 145-147)
  - World Tourists, Inc., 1949 (Reel 5248, Frame 148-150)
  - Worrell, Julia B. F., 1965 (Reel 5248, Frame 151-153)
  - Worrell, Richard, undated, 1946-1953 (Reel 5248, Frame 154-171)
  - Wovschin, Flora Don, 1944 (Reel 5248, Frame 172-175)
  - WPA Miscellaneous, 1938-1941 (Reel 5248, Frame 176-212)
    see also: Black, Ruby; Citizens Committee for Government Art Projects; Federal Arts Project; Federal Fine Arts Project; Federal Writers Project; Roosevelt, Franklin D. and Eleanor; War Department)
  - Wrenn, Charles, 1945 (Reel 5248, Frame 213-217)
  - Wright, Archie, 1958, 1962-1968 (Reel 5248, Frame 218-272)
    (see also: Farmers' Educational and Cooperative Union of America; and Farmers' Union of the New York Milk Shed)
  - Wright, Esther, 1968 (Reel 5248, Frame 273-278)
  - Writers Win-the-War Congress, 1942 (Reel 5248, Frame 279-281)
  - Wyeth, Andrew and Jamie, 1969-[1970] (Reel 5248, Frame 282-294)
    (regarding selling of Kent painting; Jamie's purchase of Monhegan house)
  - Yashima, Taro and Mitsu, 1950-1961 (Reel 5248, Frame 295-317)
  - Yaswen, Gordon and Selma, 1961, 1963, 1966 (Reel 5248, Frame 318-327)
  - Yesuretnam, H., 1968 (Reel 5248, Frame 328-332)
  - Yoder, Theodore, 1941 (Reel 5248, Frame 333-336)
  - Young American Artists Association, 1941 (Reel 5248, Frame 337-346)
  - Young American Writers, 1941 (Reel 5248, Frame 347-353)
  - Young, Art, 1936; 1944 (Reel 5248, Frame 354-391)
  - Young, Dan, undated (Reel 5248, Frame 392-395)
  - Young, Mr. and Mrs., 1958 (Reel 5248, Frame 396-398)
  - Young, Owen D., 1941 (Reel 5248, Frame 399-401)
  - Young Progressives of New York, 1949 (Reel 5248, Frame 402-405)
  - Young, Robert R., 1949 (Reel 5248, Frame 406-408)
  - Young Wives Crusade, 1940 (Reel 5248, Frame 409-413)
  - Youth, 1944 (Reel 5248, Frame 414-439)
    (mainly printed matter)
  - Youth Arts Forum, 1941 (Reel 5248, Frame 440-445)
  - Youth in Focus, 1941 (Reel 5248, Frame 446-456)
  - Youth Workshop, 1940-1941 (Reel 5248, Frame 457-463)
  - Youth's Telescope, 1944 (Reel 5248, Frame 464-469)
  - Yugoslav Embassy, 1946 (Reel 5248, Frame 470-474)
  - Yugoslav Information Center, 1950 (Reel 5248, Frame 475-482)
  - Yukon Jake Case, 1928-1931 (Reel 5248, Frame 483-530)
    (concerning copyright problem)
  - Zaborovsky, Frank, 1959-1966 (Reel 5248, Frame 531-650)
    (correspondence with Russian friend about family news, gift of Kent Collection to the USSR, exhibition, politics, requests for advice concerning granddaughter Tasha's proposed stay in Russia; see also: Russian Correspondence)
  - Zacker, The Rev. John Lewis, D.D., 1953, undated (Reel 5248, Frame 651-656)
  - Zahn, Mabel, 1948 (Reel 5248, Frame 657-662)
  - Zahn, Mrs., 1964 (Reel 5248, Frame 663-665)
  - Zakhariew, Mr., 1959 (Reel 5248, Frame 666-668)
  - Zakheim, Bernard, 1963 (Reel 5248, Frame 672-684)
  - Zalamea, Jorge, 1958 (Reel 5248, Frame 669-671)
  - Zanheiser, Howard, 1963 (Reel 5248, Frame 685-688)
  - Zarkevich, Nina, 1967-1970, undated (Reel 5248, Frame 689-718)
  - Zaumetzer, Mrs. Jessie, 1950 (Reel 5248, Frame 719-721)
  - Zeitlin, Jake, 1941, 1943, 1950-1967 (Reel 5248, Frame 722-759)
  - Zhukov, G., undated (Reel 5248, Frame 760-763)
  - Ziferstein, Dr. Isidore, 1963, [1969], undated (Reel 5248, Frame 764-788)
  - Zigrosser, Carl, 1912-1971 (Reel 5248, Frame 789-1226)
    (correspondence about New York art scene, mutual friends, Kent's painting and writing, politics, Zigrosser's activities at E. Weyhe and the Philadelphia Museum of Art; correspondence with Sally after Rockwell's death about Kent museum and care of farm; see also: American Artists Group; E. Weyhe)
  - Zilliacus, K., 1950, 1959-1962 (Reel 5248, Frame 1227-1368)
    (correspondence about Cold War and Yugoslavia, international politics, texts of articles by Zlliacus; see also: Tito v. Stalin)
  - Zinn, Mr., 1951 (Reel 5248, Frame 1369-1371)
  - Zundel, Eugenia, 1956-1968, undated (Reel 5248, Frame 1372-1407)
  - Zweig, Michael, 1958 (Reel 5248, Frame 1408-1417)
  - Unidentified and Illegible (Reel 5248)
    - Agnes, 1966 (Reel 5248, Frame 1421)
    - Agnus, 1966 (Reel 5248, Frame 1420)
    - Aileen, 1945-1946, 1956 (Reel 5248, Frame 1422-1427)
    - Albert, 1950 (Reel 5248, Frame 1428)
    - Albert, 1968 (Reel 5248, Frame 1429-1430)
    - Aleck, undated (Reel 5248, Frame 1431)
    - Alex, 1936 (Reel 5248, Frame 1434)
    - Alexy, 1971 (Reel 5248, Frame 1432-1433)
    - Alice, 1946 (Reel 5248, Frame 1435)
    - Andree, 1933 (Reel 5248, Frame 1436-1438)
    - Anna, 1942 (Reel 5248, Frame 1439)
    - Anne, 1946 (Reel 5248, Frame 1440-1443)
    - Anne and Barney, 1945 (Reel 5248, Frame 1444-1446)
    - B., undated (Reel 5248, Frame 1447)
    - Bale, undated, (scanned with Reel 5248, Frames 1448-1450) (Reel 5248)
    - Benjamin, undated (Reel 5248, Frame 1448-1450)
    - Bill, 1948, 1955 (Reel 5248, Frame 1451-1452)
    - Billie, 1949 (Reel 5248, Frame 1453-1454)
    - Bob, 1947-1948 (Reel 5248, Frame 1455-1456)
    - Brad, 1969 (Reel 5248, Frame 1457-1458)
    - Charles, 1951, 1960 (Reel 5248, Frame 1459-1462)
    - Claire, [1967] (Reel 5248, Frame 1463-1465)
    - Clark, undated (Reel 5248, Frame 1466-1467)
    - Commodore (see: Dear friends), 1968 (Reel 5249)
    - Cress, 1960 (Reel 5248, Frame 1468-1471)
    - Dale, undated (Reel 5248, Frame 1472-1473)
    - Dan, 1969 (Reel 5248, Frame 1474)
    - Dan and Fannie, 1956 (Reel 5248, Frame 1475)
    - Dan and Rose, 1952 (Reel 5248, Frame 1476)
    - Dave, 1950, 1953, 1957 (Reel 5248, Frame 1477-1479)
    - David, 1953 (Reel 5248, Frame 1480-1483)
    - Dear friends (also Commodore), 1953 (Reel 5249, Frame 321-322)
    - Dee, 1961 (Reel 5248, Frame 1484-1487)
    - Dee Dee, 1968 (Reel 5248, Frame 1488-1489)
    - Dick, 1948 (Reel 5248, Frame 1490-1491)
    - Dick, 1967 (Reel 5248, Frame 1492)
    - Dick and Bernice, 1954 (Reel 5248, Frame 1493)
    - Dixie, 1959 (Reel 5248, Frame 1494)
    - Don and Sigrid, 1961 (Reel 5248, Frame 1495)
    - Doris, undated (Reel 5248, Frame 1496-1497)
    - Dorothy, 1963, undated (Reel 5248, Frame 1498-1506)
    - Dot, 1966 (Reel 5248, Frame 1507)
    - Doug and Harry, 1963 (Reel 5248, Frame 1508)
    - Ed, 1968 (Reel 5248, Frame 1509-1510)
    - Edith, undated (Reel 5248, Frame 1511)
    - Edmund, 1950 (Reel 5248, Frame 1512-1513)
    - Eileen [Aileen?] and Guy, 1955-1961 (Reel 5248, Frame 1520-1531)
    - Eleanor, 1934 (Reel 5248, Frame 1514-1516)
    - Eleanor, 1945 (Reel 5248, Frame 1532-1533)
    - Elizabeth, 1963 (Reel 5248, Frame 1517-1518)
    - Ellen, undated (Reel 5248, Frame 1534-1537)
    - Eric, 1969 (Reel 5248, Frame 1519)
    - Ernestine, 1947, 1950 (Reel 5248, Frame 1538-1544)
    - Ernst and Thea, 1946 (Reel 5248, Frame 1545)
    - Erwin and Janet, 1961 (Reel 5248, Frame 1546-1548)
    - Flora, 1945 (Reel 5248, Frame 1550)
    - Florence, 1966 (Reel 5248, Frame 1551-1552)
    - Francie, 1959 (Reel 5248, Frame 1553)
    - Franzi, 1959-1961, 1969; undated (Reel 5248, Frame 1554-1572)
    - Franzi, cont. (Reel 5249, Frame 4-5)
    - Georgia, 1948-1949, 1958 (Reel 5249, Frame 6-9)
    - Gertrude, undated (Reel 5249, Frame 10-11)
    - Gladys, 1953 (Reel 5249, Frame 12-13)
    - Guess Who, undated (Reel 5249, Frame 323-324)
    - Gwen, 1953 (Reel 5249, Frame 14)
    - Hans, 1957 (Reel 5249, Frame 15-17)
    - Harold, 1957, undated (Reel 5249, Frame 18-23)
    - Harry, 1950, 1960 (Reel 5249, Frame 24-25)
    - Helen, 1956 (Reel 5249, Frame 26-27)
    - Henry, 1964 (Reel 5249, Frame 28-30)
    - Henry and Agnes, 1948 (Reel 5249, Frame 31-34)
    - Hilde, 1968 (Reel 5249, Frame 35)
    - Howard, 1950 (Reel 5249, Frame 36-38)
    - Irene, 1958 (Reel 5249, Frame 39)
    - Jack, 1960 (Reel 5249, Frame 40)
    - Jane, 1954, 1958 (Reel 5249, Frame 41-46)
    - Jean, 1955 (Reel 5249, Frame 47)
    - Jean and George, undated (Reel 5249, Frame 48-49)
    - Jenny, undated (Reel 5249, Frame 50-54)
    - Jessica, 1966 (Reel 5249, Frame 55)
    - Jim, 1954 (Reel 5249, Frame 56)
    - Jim and Margaret, 1946 (Reel 5249, Frame 57)
    - Joe, 1961-1962 (Reel 5249, Frame 58-80)
    - John, 1950, 1953, 1960-1961 (Reel 5249, Frame 81-86)
    - Joyce, undated (Reel 5249, Frame 87)
    - June, undated (Reel 5249, Frame 88-89)
    - Kasana, 1965-1966, undated (Reel 5249, Frame 90-120)
    - Kay, 1944 (Reel 5249, Frame 121)
    - Keith and Leila, 1958 (Reel 5249, Frame 122)
    - Kent, undated (Reel 5249, Frame 123-124)
    - Lanky, 1956 (Reel 5249, Frame 126)
    - Leif, 1957 (Reel 5249, Frame 127)
    - Leo, 1951 (Reel 5249, Frame 128)
    - Leon, 1956, 1965 (Reel 5249, Frame 129-131)
    - Leonard, 1957 (Reel 5249, Frame 132-133)
    - Libus, 1968 (Reel 5249, Frame 134)
    - Lily, 1913 (Reel 5249, Frame 135-136)
    - Linc, 1954, 1957, 1961 (Reel 5249, Frame 137-141)
    - Linda, 1961 (Reel 5249, Frame 142-144)
    - Louis, 1948, 1953 (Reel 5249, Frame 145-147)
    - Ludwig, 1944 (Reel 5249, Frame 148)
    - Lydia, 1952 (Reel 5249, Frame 149)
    - Lynn, 1964 (Reel 5249, Frame 150)
    - Margaret, 1950, 1961 (Reel 5249, Frame 151-153)
    - Margaret and Nils, 1951, 1955, 1958 (Reel 5249, Frame 209-222)
    - Maria, 1954 (Reel 5249, Frame 154-155)
    - Marian, undated (Reel 5249, Frame 160-161)
    - Marie, undated (Reel 5249, Frame 156)
    - Marion, 1947 (Reel 5249, Frame 157-159)
    - Mary, 1950, 1952, 1959 (Reel 5249, Frame 162-171)
    - Mary and Steve, 1951 (Reel 5249, Frame 172)
    - Marya, 1925 (Reel 5741, Frame 44-52)
      (previously sealed love letter)
    - Max and Lola, 1952, 1959-1961 (Reel 5249, Frame 173-184)
    - May, 1955, 1958 (Reel 5249, Frame 185-189)
    - Moose, 1947 (Reel 5249, Frame 190)
    - Naomi, 1960 (Reel 5249, Frame 191-192)
    - Natasha and Muir, 1962-1963 (Reel 5249, Frame 205-208)
    - Nate and Anna, 1957-1958 (Reel 5249, Frame 193-204)
    - Norman, 1952 (Reel 5249, Frame 223)
    - Pauline, 1948 (Reel 5249, Frame 225-228)
    - Peggy, 1945 (Reel 5249, Frame 229)
    - Pete and Catharine, 1957 (Reel 5249, Frame 230-237)
    - Philippa, 1958-1959, undated (Reel 5249, Frame 238-270)
    - Polly, undated (Reel 5249, Frame 271-272)
    - Ralfred, 1948 (Reel 5249, Frame 273)
    - Renee, 1956 (Reel 5249, Frame 274)
    - Rita, undated (Reel 5249, Frame 276)
    - Russie, undated (Reel 5249, Frame 275)
    - Sam, 1952, 1956, 1961 (Reel 5249, Frame 277-282)
    - Shirley, undated (Reel 5249, Frame 283-284)
    - Steve, 1970 (Reel 5249, Frame 285)
    - Steve and Ruth, 1952 (Reel 5249, Frame 286)
    - Syd and Bunny, 1968 (Reel 5249, Frame 287-288)
    - Sylvia, undated (Reel 5249, Frame 289)
    - Ted and Ida, 1953 (Reel 5249, Frame 290)
    - Thelma, 1961-1965 (Reel 5249, Frame 291-295)
    - Tom and Elizabeth, 1968 (Reel 5249, Frame 296-299)
    - Vera and Dick, 1967 (Reel 5249, Frame 300)
    - Vivian, Irving, Paula, Bette, and Douglas, 1957 (Reel 5249, Frame 301-302)
    - Wade, 1949 (Reel 5249, Frame 303-306)
    - Wallie, 1947 (Reel 5249, Frame 307)
    - Walter, 1959-1960 (Reel 5249, Frame 308-309)
    - Walter, Leslie, and Alice, 1905 (Reel 5249, Frame 310-311)
    - Illegible, 1914-1961, undated (Reel 5249, Frame 325-373)